0401
火
0501
木
It's the beginning of Golden Week. The construction for Shuuichi's new house is about to start.

Everyone's gathered at the construction site today as a kind of ribbon-cutting ceremony.

Shuuichi
「So our home is finally going to be built here on this plot.」
％Ｂ
「Yeah, that's right.」
Shuuichi
「Oh man... I'm so happy I could die!」
％Ｂ
「Oh, come on. Don't jinx things before construction even starts.」
Miyamoto
「Hey there.」
％Ｂ
「Oh, President Miyamoto. I'll be counting on you once more for this.」
Miyamoto
「And I'm happy to get to work with you again too. I heard this was a commission from a friend of yours...?」

％Ｂ
「Yes, this is the client for this job, Nirasawa. Shuuichi, this is Miyamoto-san, the manager of the Miyamoto Group, who's going to be handling the construction for your house.」

Miyamoto
「I'm Miyamoto. I very much look forward to working with you.」
Shuuichi
「Oh no, likewise, I look forward to working with you!」
Miyamoto
「If this was for a friend, then I'm sure that means you must've gone the extra mile on the design. We'll put everything we have into our work, so both you and your client can be satisfied.」


％Ｂ
「Yes, thank you very much!」
I head straight back to the office after greeting everyone.
I upload photos from the ribbon-cutting ceremony onto my blog and send Shuuichi an email with a link to the page.

I'll let Miyamoto-san handle Shuuichi's stuff for now. I need to get working on the cultural hall job I got from Azuma-san next.

I start gathering up the rough concept sketches I drew out when I had time earlier at work.

％Ｂ
「I need to at least decide on a general direction.」
I place the papers in my bag and head to the Azuma Architectural Firm.

Azuma
「Rejected.」
％Ｂ
「Gh...」
He barely even glanced at the rough drafts.
Azuma
「No good at all. In fact, none of them are any good. Rejected, all of them.」
A complete rejection.
I remember he used to do the same thing to me a lot back when I had just joined his firm...

Wait, no! Now's not the time to be waxing nostalgic!
％Ｂ
「Um... I know they're all rough concepts without any details, but I just thought it would be good to decide on a general direction for now.」

Azuma
「I know that, and they're rejected.」
％Ｂ
「Wha...!? What wasn't good about them?」
Azuma
「Figure it out yourself.」
Yep, right...
This is the same as before too.
Now I remember...
Azuma
「Were you seriously thinking I'd okay these?」
％Ｂ
「I wasn't looking for an okay, I just wanted to figure out where I should go with things. I thought that maybe one of them might strike a chord with you.」


Azuma
「What's the point of seeing how I feel about it? Is it just me, or has your sense of aesthetics gotten duller since you left? I think you had better designs back when you worked here.」


％Ｂ
「...」
I have to say, that annoys me just a little to hear.
I don't like the way how he's making it sound like it was a mistake for me to become independent.
％Ｂ
「...I understand. I'll bring something that will satisfy you next time, Teacher.」

Azuma
「Yeah, do that. I'm a busy man. Don't waste my time too much, all right?」

％Ｂ
「...I'll be excusing myself, then.」
％Ｂ
「Sigh... No good, I guess...」
They may have just been general rough concepts, but getting all of them rejected's a bit depressing...
％Ｂ
「...Still though, Teacher seemed like he was in a bad mood.」
I wonder if he was on edge because he's got too much work on his hands.
The way he was talking today seemed a little harsh.
％Ｂ
「No... He's not someone who'd get like that just 'cause he's busy.」
％Ｂ
「Either way though, onto the next thing!」
There's no point in getting depressed.
I've never done anything like designing a mid-size hall before. What's there to do but charge forward and keep at it?

％Ｂ
「I'm gonna do it, dammit!」
I'll bring something that'll satisfy Azuma-san next time, for sure!
dummy
_00com
bgm51
bgm51
bg510
bg510
_00grp
bg510
_00bup
bs_sy01_10
_00bup
bs_sy01_03
_00bup
bs_sy01_06
_00grp
_00grp
bg419
_00grp
_00grp
bg408
_00bup
bs_az01_1004
_00bup
bs_az01_04
_00bup
_00bup
bs_az01_08
_00bup
bs_az01_06
_00bup
bs_az11_08
_00bup
bs_az11_05
_00bup
bs_az01_08
_00bup
_00bup
bs_az01_0504
_00bup
bs_az01_06
_00grp
bgm17
bgm17
_00grp
bg312_01
bg501
_00grp
_00com
