0913
日
0801
水
Natsuki
「Oh, there you are. Heeey!」
％Ｂ
「Yo, Segawa. Long time no see.」
Natsuki
「Seriouslyyy. Where's Sora?」
％Ｂ
「I think she's probably in the waiting room already.」
Natsuki
「Aw, I wanted her to see everyone first though.」
％Ｂ
「She is still at work, you know.」
Natsuki
「Hey everyone! He's over here!」
all
Marika
「Wooow～ It's been forever!」
％Ｂ
「Oh, Shinozaki. Nice seeing you again.」

Misa
「It has been far too long.」
％Ｂ
「Thank you very much for your help before, Senpai.」
all
Touko
「I don't think you've seen me in over ten years, right?」
％Ｂ
「Yeah, you're right... I think it has been about that long, Yukimura.」

Rikka
「We've met a little more recently.」
％Ｂ
「Thanks for all your help with the Shionagi Cultural Hall.」
all
Having a conversation for the first time in a while with all of my friends is nice.
We had everyone come here today for one reason.
The science museum that had been temporarily closed is finally to reopen today.

I tried asking everyone if they could come see the first planetarium show.

To be honest, I wasn't sure if everyone would come.
We all have our own work schedules to juggle, especially since today's a weekday.
The fact that every single one of us came to watch in spite of that fills my heart with gratitude.

Shuuichi
「Let's get going already!」
％Ｂ
「Yeah, you're right. Let's go.」
We all sit in a row.
The planetarium's already completely full for the first showing after the reopening.

％Ｂ
「Oh...」
Marika
「Looks like it's about to start～」
Sora appears as the navigator.
She spots us right away, and smiles brightly at us.
The lights turn off, and the room falls silent.
I can hear oohs and aahs from the kids as the stars glimmer into visibility on the ceiling.

Sora
「...Welcome to the newly reborn planetarium. I am happy from the bottom of my heart to be able to see all of you here once more.」


Sora
「Many things have changed here in the newly built science museum. From the seats you are sitting in, to the ceiling screen, and to the projection machine, everything has become brand new.」


Sora
「However, there are also many things in this world which do not change. Our hearts, for example. Our feelings for the people we love, our wishes to keep them close, will never change.」


...Yeah. We've spent such a long time together.
But those feelings won't ever change...
It all started with one small encounter, and led all the way here.
They might each be small, trivial memories.
But some of them were enough to change our lives.
They're like the stars that glitter in the night sky...
And by connecting all of them together, a story is born...
We're still here... Nothing's changed.
Sora
「The stars move through the sky, showing us once more their unchanging light. Just like they did in the distant past, they accept your wishes, and make them come true...」


That's right... The stars grant wishes.
My wishes... Sora's wishes...
...All of our wishes.
dummy
_00com
bgm32
bgm32
bg501
_00grp
bg312_01
_00bup
bs_nt01_02
_00bup
_00bup
bs_nt01_02
_00bup
bs_nt01_01
_00bup
bs_nt02_1004
_00bup
bs_nt01_02
all
_00bup
_00bup
all
_00bup
bs_mr01_02
_00bup
_00bup
bs_ms01_01
all
_00bup
_00bup
all
_00bup
bs_tk01_02
_00bup
_00bup
bs_rk01_02
all
_00bup
_00bup
all
_00bup
bs_sy01_02
_00grp
_00bup
bs_mr01_01
_00grp
bgm01
bgm01
cg_sr14_0244
_00grp
cg_sr14_0244
_00grp
cg_sr14_0243
_00grp
cg_sr14_0233
_00grp
cg_sr14_0244
_00grp
cg_sr01_0101
_00grp
cg_sr03_0133
_00grp
cg_sr14_0133
_00grp
cg_sr14_0233
_00grp
cg_sr14_0214
_00grp
cg_sr14_0214
_00grp
cg_sr14_0414
_00grp
_00grp
_00com
