I gently place my lips on hers.
Sora
「Mm...」
She lets me kiss her. She doesn't show even a hint of disliking it.

Sora
「Nh... mh...～～～」
Her faint breaths from her nose brush against my cheeks.
It's comfortably ticklish.
Sora
「...～～ ..nh... Mmh...～～」
I slowly pull away.
％Ｂ
「...Hahh...」
Sora
「...Again.」
％Ｂ
「Hm?」
Sora
「...I want to kiss... again.」
％Ｂ
「Yeah... Sure...」
I kiss her once more.
Sora
「...Mm...nh...」
Her lips are soft.
I hear girls' lips described as "like marshmallows" a lot. I get why.

Sora
「Nh... mmh... nh...～～～」
Hahh... I feel like... I'm gonna melt...
Sora
「...～～～...nh... fh...」
％Ｂ
「Fhh...」
Sora
「...Again.」
％Ｂ
「Wha... S-Sure...」
We kiss for the third time.
Sora
「～～～...mh...nh...～～...～～～」
...I guess Sora likes kissing?
I mean, I do too, of course.
Sora
「Chu...～～～...～～」
I'm happy she wants to kiss me so much.
Because I want to kiss her too...
Sora
「...Nh...～～... nnh... fhh...」
％Ｂ
「...Nh... Pfah...」
Sora
「...I want more.」
％Ｂ
「...Do you like kissing?」
Sora
「...*nod*」
Sora
「...I like kissing you... It makes me feel warm...」

Sora
「...I like kissing you... It makes me feel warm...」

％Ｂ
「...」
Sora
「...We can't?」
％Ｂ
「Of course we can...」
Our fourth kiss.
Sora
「Mm...～...～～...」
...She likes kissing me, she says?
It makes her feel warm, she says?
Aghh, dammit... She's just so cute...
How could my girlfriend possibly be this cute?
This is just gonna make me wanna kiss her forever.
Sora
「Mm...nkh...～～～ Fh...nh...～～～」
I pull her even closer.
Sora
「Mm...nh...～～～ Nnh...」
Sora's actually pretty soft...
Well, of course she is.
She might be small, but she's still a girl...
Sora
「Chu...～～～ ...Mh...nh...」
The girl I love is in my arms.
And I keep giving her countless kisses.
Having these tender thighs so close to me feels so good.
How am I supposed to contain myself?
Sora
「Nnh...」
I'm rock hard just from kissing.
Can't really blame a healthy young man for getting this way after four whole kisses.
But maybe Sora would be totally grossed out if she noticed...
％Ｂ
「...」
I try casually pulling my hips back as we kiss, so Sora won't notice.

All right. This way she won't―
Sora
「...No pulling away...」
She pulls herself closer.
％Ｂ
「Wait... Um...」
Sora
「...?? I can feel something.」
％Ｂ
「Uhh... Well, you see...」
Sora pulls away a little to take a look at the unfamiliar presence.
Sora
「...」
What am I gonna do if she's grossed out...?
Sora
「...It's up.」
She's definitely not wrong.
％Ｂ
「...I'm a guy, after all... That's just gonna happen if I kiss the girl I like a lot.」

Sora
「...It's hard.」
％Ｂ
「It's proof that it's functional as a male reproductive organ...」
Sora
「...It's hot.」
％Ｂ
「It's proof that I'm alive...」
Sora
「...」
％Ｂ
「...Uh... What do I say... I'm sorry.」
Sora
「...*shake shake*... No issues.」
She closes her eyes and kisses me again.
I guess this really must not be any issue for her.
I resume my kiss with Sora.
Sora
「...～～～... Fh, nh... nnh...」
...Speaking of which... Is it okay for me to use my tongue and stuff?
Maybe?
Maybe not?
Sora
「...Chu... Mmh～～」
Guess I'll give it a try...
I gently stick my tongue out from between my lips as we kiss.
Sora
「...Nh...～～～ ...Nh...」
The tip of my tongue makes contact with her lips.
She doesn't really react.
I'll just keep going, into her mouth―
Sora
「...Mmh...Nh...!」
She twitches in response.
Maybe not...?
Sora
「...Mh～～～...nh...」
She parts her lips and lets my tongue in.
Sora
「...Chu... nkh, chu...mlh...」
I extend my tongue and explore the inside of her mouth.
I encounter a hot, soft object.
This... must be Sora's tongue.
Sora
「...Mlh... Chu... Mh～～～ ...Fh, nh...」
I tickle her tongue with mine.
But she doesn't try to move her tongue against mine.
Maybe it's a little embarrassing for her...?
Though I'm glad that she doesn't seem to dislike it, at least.
Sora
「Mlh... mh... mlph... Mh～～～ Chu, nh...」
The wet sound of our kissing tickles against my ear.
...I wonder... how far I'm allowed to go?
Kissing's okay, obviously.
Using my tongue wasn't a problem either.
Then next would be―
To touch her breasts
To continue kissing
％Ｂ
「...」
I slowly move my hand that I have around her toward her hips.
Sora
「...Nh...!」
She twitches in response again.
But she doesn't stop me.
Next would have to be her chest... Her boobs...
I wonder if it's okay for me to touch her there.
Actually, I wonder how long it takes for a relationship to progress to that point.
Sora
「...Nh... chu... Mmh... fhh... mlhchu... mmph...」
There's no way there's any kind of hard rule...
If there's no rule...
Then that would mean that touching now wouldn't be an issue... probably.
％Ｂ
「...Gulp...」
I ride the momentum of the kiss and place my hand on Sora's chest.
Sora
「...Mmh...」
Oh. She's frowning.
Maybe she doesn't like this...?
％Ｂ
「Pfah... Not okay?」
Sora
「...Touching is okay...」
Touching is?
％Ｂ
「So then what's not okay?」
Sora
「...They're small.」
％Ｂ
「Hm? Small?」
Sora
「...My breasts are below average when compared to females of the same age group...」
Sora
「...I don't come even close to Misa... I can't win against Natsu or Tou... My chest is so much smaller than Mari's or Ritsu's...」

Those are some pretty specific comparisons...
％Ｂ
「...Ah...」
Now I remember they were all comparing boob sizes in the hot spring when we went camping.
That must be why.
％Ｂ
「...Sora.」
I say her name gently, and place my hand on her chest.
I don't rub or fondle. I just gently place my hand on top.
Sora
「...Ryou...?」
Sora
「...Mm...?」
％Ｂ
「Doing this is warm and comforting. And... it just makes me happy.」

Sora
「Ryou... Does touching my chest make you happy?」
Sora
「Does... touching my chest make you happy?」
％Ｂ
「Yeah. It does. It just fills me up inside.」
Sora
「...Really. That makes me feel the same way.」
％Ｂ
「I'm glad we both feel the same.」
I kiss her once more, to fill her with happiness.
Sora
「Mm...～～...」
And while we kiss―
I try squeezing just a little.
Sora
「Nh...～～～...!?」
Oh. She looks a little surprised.
But she doesn't look like she wants me to stop.
Sora
「Mh...nh... Mmh... fh... nnh... nh...」
I can hear her moan a little through her lips against mine.
Sora
「...Mh...nh... Mmh...～～ ...Fh...nh... nnh...」
She's probably trying to hide her reactions.
But that stubbornness is just getting me more excited.
Sora
「...Kh... Mmh...nh...nnh... Fh...～～～ ...Fh, aah...」
My brain feels like it's boiling from the heat of her breaths against my cheek.
％Ｂ
「...」
Kissing → Okay
Tongue → No problem
Touch her boobs → Success!
Which means next would be―
Below, maybe...?
Sora
「Nmh... Mm～～～ ...Nh... mmh... Fhh...nh...」
But... Is that really okay?
I've just been getting bolder and bolder because Sora's been letting me do everything so far...

But is it really okay for me to move forward like this?
If we end up going all the way like this... I don't have any condoms or anything...

But if I stop here, then I would feel bad after Sora wrung out her courage for all this...

Sora
「...Chu... chmh... mmh... chu... fh...nh... Aah...」
...There's no point in thinking.
Let's just go with the flow.
％Ｂ
「...」
I casually move my hand away from her boobs, downward.

I place my hand in the hem of her skirt─
Sora
「Nh... nnh...!?」
％Ｂ
「Gh...!」
Sora tenses up all at once the moment I touch her there.
She's squeezed her thighs together tight to prevent my hand from moving any further.
％Ｂ
「Pfah... Sora?」
Sora
「...」
She's biting her lip and looking downward, her face bright red.
I guess this was too much...
％Ｂ
「...Sorry. I'll pull my hand away, so could you let go?」
Sora
「...Oh...」
I pull my hand back after Sora relaxes.
％Ｂ
「...Sorry for rushing into things. You're not mentally prepared yet, right?」
Sora
「...*shake shake*... I was just a little surprised... No issues...」

％Ｂ
「You don't have to force yourself.」
Sora
「...I'm not. I really was just surprised...」
％Ｂ
「...Either way, I think we should still stop here for today.」

Sora
「...Why...?」
％Ｂ
「Mm... Truth is, I don't have any condoms or anything. If we're gonna do stuff like this, I'm sure we have to do it properly.」

Sora
「...」
％Ｂ
「And besides, I'm happy enough just doing this for now.」
I hug her tight.
％Ｂ
「...You're here in my arms... That's enough for me.」
Sora
「...Ryou.」
Sora
「...Mmh.」
She presses her head against my chest.
She looks up at me and―
Sora
「...What's going to happen with this hot and hard thing?」
％Ｂ
「...Well, uh... I'll do something about it later...」
Sora
「...What are you―」
％Ｂ
「No details. It's a man's secret. Okay?」
Sora
「...*nod*」
She nods obediently.
I feel it's still too early to go to the next base.
％Ｂ
「...」
There's no need to rush. We'll have plenty of time in the future.
We can take all the time in the world for our love to blossom.
And so, we spend the day doing nothing but kiss.
The sun begins to set, its crimson light dyeing my room. 
However, our faces are much more red than any sunset.
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「We've kissed so much...」
Sora
「Umhm」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「That was amazing. Thanks.」
Sora
「Umhm」
Sora
「...」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Hmm?」
Sora is staring intently at me.
It feels like so wants to say something.
Does she want to kiss one more time?
Sora
「Do you want... more?」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Huh...?」
Sora
「Kisses aren't enough to satisfy a teenage boy.」
Sora
「If 
Ryou wants 
 you want 
 more, then...」
Sora's face reddens even more as she hangs her head down.
I'm elated hearing that from Sora.
I embrace her without thinking.

Sora
「Nnh...!?」
Sora stiffens as I hold her.
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Ah, sorry. I was just so happy hearing that.」
Sora
「Hehe... You just surprised me... that's all.」
With that, Sora stops resisiting.
It makes me so glad that Sora is doing her best to being so bold.
However...
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「I don't want to force anything on you. It's fine if we take it slow.」
Sora
「You aren't forcing anything... It's just that...」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Just that?」
Sora
「Hmmm～～～」
Sora hesitates before averting her gaze and mumbling.

Sora
「...They're small.」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Hm? Small?」
Well, she does have a small frame.
Out of all the first years, she'd probably be one of the smallest.
She might even be the smallest.
Sora
「...My breasts are below average when compared to females of the same age group...」
Sora
「...I don't come even close to Misa... I can't win against Natsu or Tou... My chest is so much smaller than Mari's or Ritsu's...」

Oh... she means that.
Sora
「My chest might not meet 
Ryou's 
 your 
 expectations...」
She sounds dejected.
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Come on, give me a break...」
I pull her in for a tight hug.
Because of her height, her head is snug against my chest.
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Can you hear my heart beating?」
Sora
「Nnh...？　Umhm...」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「It becomes like this when I start hugging you.」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「If I start touching your breasts, my heart will beat even faster.」
Sora
「Because you'll be aroused?」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「That and because I'll be happy.」
Sora
「If I can make 
Ryou 
 you 
 happy... then I'll be happy as well.」
Sora relaxes a bit and the tension in her cheeks slowly dissipates.
Sora
「Want to do it...?」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Thanks Sora... but I think that'll be enough for today.」
I give her a kiss in response.
Sora
「Hmm... Uuh... But...
Ryou, 
 
you're hard...」
She's definitely feeling it hit her through our hug.
Sora
「I'll... be fine.」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「I really appreciate it.」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「But... I didn't buy any condoms.」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Doing it without one would be a terrible idea.」
Sora
「...」
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「What we did right now makes me plenty satisfied.」
I gently stroke Sora's cheeks.
％Ｂ＿ＣＳ
「Being able to hug you right now is enough for me.」
Sora
「...
Ryou
Umhm
...」
Understanding my happiness, Sora nods in response.
So, she closes her eyes and lifts her jaw.
Returning her affection, I give Sora a kiss.
Sora
「Thank you
, Ryou

...」
Being able to see her genuinely smile gives me so much bliss.
I feel our bond strengthening, becoming stronger than before.
I'll make sure that I cherish her even more in the future, cross my heart and hope to die.
dummy
_00com
bgm37
bgm37
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010204
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010501
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00com
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010501
_00grp
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010501
_00grp
cg_sr07_010201
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_010101
_00grp
cg_sr07_010205
_00grp
cg_sr07_010501
_00grp
cg_sr07_010503
_00grp
cg_sr07_010103
_00grp
cg_sr07_010503
_00grp
cg_sr07_010103
_00grp
cg_sr07_020103
_00grp
cg_sr07_020505
_00grp
cg_sr07_010505
_00grp
cg_sr07_010201
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
cg_sr07_020401
_00com
_00grp
cg_sr07_020404
_00com
_00grp
cg_sr07_020101
_00grp
cg_sr07_020501
_00grp
cg_sr07_020103
_00grp
cg_sr07_020504
_00grp
cg_sr07_020103
_00grp
cg_sr07_020503
_00grp
cg_sr07_020505
_00grp
cg_sr07_020404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00com
_00grp
cg_sr07_010405
_00grp
cg_sr07_010404
_00grp
cg_sr07_010401
_00grp
bgm35
bgm35
_00grp
bg201e
_00bup
bu_sr03_10
_00bup
bu_sr03_1001
_00bup
bu_sr03_1003
_00bup
bu_sr03_01
_00bup
bu_sr03_0701
_00bup
bu_sr03_0704
_00bup
bu_sr03_10
_00com
_00bup
bu_sr01_0910
_00bup
bu_sr01_0602
_00bup
bu_sr01_07
_00bup
bu_sr01_06
_00bup
bu_sr02_07
_00bup
bu_sr02_06
_00bup
bu_sr02_07
_00bup
bu_sr02_06
_00com
_00bup
bu_sr03_09
_00bup
bu_sr03_0901
_00bup
bu_sr03_0904
_00bup
bu_sr03_03
_00com
_00bup
bu_sr03_10
_00bup
bu_sr03_0810
_00bup
bu_sr03_0701
_00com
_00bup
bu_sr02_10
_00bup
bu_sr02_04
_00bup
bu_sr02_1011
_00com
_00bup
bu_sr02_11
_00com
_00grp
_00grp
_00com
