0705
土
0711
金
$$smh_OpenCHK
The last day of finals.
I go to the second chemistry classroom immediately after finishing my last subject.

I'm here to check over the math answers that I'm unsure about, together with Okihara-senpai.
％Ｂ
「Wh-What do you think?」
Misa
「Well... Let's check through them together.」
all
She marks her way through the answers I copied down from memory onto an answer sheet with a red pen.

All of my self-scores have been over 70 percent so far.
I won't have to take supplementary lessons as long as I haven't screwed up math.
Misa
「...I'm done.」
％Ｂ
「Okay...」
all
She writes my score onto the answer sheet.
My score for math is...
72 percent!
％Ｂ
「All right!」
No supplementary lessons for me!
Misa
「Congratulations!」
I sigh in relief at her congratulatory smile.
％Ｂ
「Hahhh... Thank god...」
I'm so glad I had her teach me.
I'm nothing compared to someone who consistently places in the top five like her, but I've somehow managed to scrape by with scores that let me stand proud... I think.

％Ｂ
「I'm glad I didn't end up failing anything... I wouldn't have the time to help prepare for the Tanabata Festival if I had to take supplementary lessons.」


％Ｂ
「It's all thanks to you, Okihara-senpai! Thank you so very much!」
Misa
「Oh no, I didn't do that much at all. It was all because of your hard work, Ryousuke-san.」

Misa
「Oh no, I didn't do that much at all. It was all because of your hard work.」

％Ｂ
「No, it was because you were so good at teaching.」
Misa
「No, it's because you were so quick at learning
, Ryousuke-san

.」
％Ｂ
「Oh no, it was because... You know what, let's not do this.」

Misa
「Hehe... Yes, let's not. It's a bit strange.」
％Ｂ
「And now we'll be able to start actually preparing for the festival.」
There's less than a month before the Tanabata Festival.
Now that we've gotten permission to use the old school building, things are looking to get busy.
％Ｂ
「Let's do our best!」
Misa
「Yes, let's! Oh, but before that...」

％Ｂ
「...Huh?」
She brings her lips up to my ear.
Misa
「We'll have to follow through on our promise, won't we?」
I give a start at her whisper.
％Ｂ
「P-Promise...?」
Misa
「Have you forgotten already? Then... I'll ask you once more.」

Her lips get even closer to my ear.
Misa
「Would you like... to go on a vacation together, to my secret spot?」
Her voice sends shivers down my spine. It's like she's tickling my ear with her question. And―
％Ｂ
「Y-Yes, I would!」
I find myself more or less nodding on reflex.
dummy
_00com
gakuen_chime
_02smh
bgm13
_00grp
bg111_01
_00bup
bs_ms01_04
_00bup
bs_ms01_01
all
_00bup
_00bup
all
pen1
_00bup
bs_ms01_0201
all
_00bup
_00bup
all
pen2
_00bup
bs_ms01_0206
_00bup
bs_ms01_0203
_00bup
bs_ms01_01
_00com
_00bup
bs_ms01_0106
_00com
_00bup
bs_ms01_0201
_00bup
_00bup
bs_ms01_03
_00bup
bs_ms01_06
_00bup
_00bup
bs_ms01_08
_00bup
bu_ms02_01
_00bup
bu_ms02_0402
_00bup
bu_ms02_1004
_00bup
_00bup
bu_ms02_02
_00bup
bu_ms02_0402
_00bup
bu_ms11_0201
_00grp
_00com
