0623
月
0624
火
$$smh_OpenCHK
％Ｂ
「Nnh... nnnh... aagh...」
I grope blindly to stop my alarm.
My arms feel like lead.
％Ｂ
「...I feel... kinda heavy...」
I sit up in bed.
％Ｂ
「Whoa... Everything's all warped.」
It's like someone took the familiar sight of my room and elongated it.
My breaths feel hot.
My eyelids feel heavy.
Everything just feels sluggish and heavy...
％Ｂ
「...I've gone and done it...」
I've been trying to stay as healthy as I can, since I've been living alone...

％Ｂ
「...I bet it's because of yesterday...」
I plunged into a torrential downpour to save the telescope.
I wasn't out for even a minute, but I got soaked all the way down to my underwear.

I prioritized drying the telescope over my own clothes.
And that's led to this.
％Ｂ
「...Ugh... Brrh...! It-It's so cold...?? Aghh... Crap... Do I have a thermometer?」

Or more like, do I have any medicine...?
％Ｂ
「～～Ughh～ ...I feel dizzy... I'll call the school and tell them I won't be coming in today...」

I call the school's number on my cell phone.
I hope they don't think I'm faking it if I'm calling myself in sick...
_smh_st_02
_smh_st_btn02
_smh_st_02
_smh_st_btn05
％Ｂ
「Oh... Hello? This is ％Ａ ％Ｂ, from class 2-C... Yes... Good morning... I currently have a fever... Yes... I'd like to call in sick for today... Yes...」


％Ｂ
「I'll call again depending on how I'm doing as to whether I'll be coming tomorrow... Yes... Thank you very much... Excuse me, then.」

_smh_st_04
％Ｂ
「Phew... They approved that surprisingly quickly.」
％Ｂ
「Now then... I think I'll just sleep...」
％Ｂ
「...Wait, I can't sleep yet.」
I have to take some medicine before that.
I'll need to force myself to eat something too, and I should get a sports drink or something to stay hydrated too.

％Ｂ
「And I have to do all of that myself... Living alone sucks.」

I stumble out of bed.
Let's just get everything I need ready before I get back in bed.
％Ｂ
「I'll need a change of clothes for when I get sweaty too... Sigh... This is such a pain...」
...Wait, what?
Is this... a dream?
I see... a starry sky.
Several bright stars, glittering in a deep darkness.
It's pretty... and strangely nostalgic...
It's not like the night sky's ever gone away or changed. I wonder why I feel nostalgic...?

And there's... someone next to me.
Who is it...?
Who's this... sitting next to me?
％Ｂ
「You connect that star, and that one like this and... you get the airplane constellation!」
？？？
「...That isn't a constellation.」
％Ｂ
「Then you connect that and that... The tank constellation!」
？？？
「...That's not one either.」
％Ｂ
「Ghh... Then show me a fun summer constellation.」
？？？
「...Those stars. Connect those five like a W.」
％Ｂ
「W... The W constellation!」
？？？
「...No. Cassiopeia. She's a queen from Greek mythology, and Princess Andromeda's mom.」

％Ｂ
「So she's the mom of an android princess!」
？？？
「...Princess Andromeda.」
％Ｂ
「You know lots of hard words.」
？？？
「...Mhmh.」
％Ｂ
「...Aagh...?」
％Ｂ
「...What... time is it...?」
I check my phone next to my bed.
％Ｂ
「...The hell... 5 p.m. already...」
I sit up.
％Ｂ
「...Ahh... I feel a little better... but I think I still have a fever.」
It doesn't look like my temperature's actually gone down either.
I measured 37.5 degrees after I ate breakfast earlier.
I took some over-the-counter pills and went to sleep, but it had gone up to 38.2 degrees when I checked earlier a little past noon.

％Ｂ
「...I guess the over-the-counter stuff's not good enough... I'll have to go to the doctor's if it doesn't go down tomorrow...」

％Ｂ
「Sigh... I feel like I had a kinda nostalgic dream... What was it again...?」

I forgot it already...
My thought process might be a little muddled from the fever...
I've been looking at the stars a lot with Ousaka lately, so maybe that stuff's mixing into my thoughts.

％Ｂ
「...It's still too early to take my pills for the night... I'll sleep a little more, and take them after I eat dinner...」

I burrow back into my sheets.
dummy
_00com
_00grp
_black
_02smh
clock_alarm
bgm11
bgm11
_00grp
b_bg201
b_bg201
_00grp
b_bg201
_02smh_06tell
sumaho_tsunagaru
se0024_01
se0024_01
_02smh_auto
_00grp
_00grp
_00grp
b_bg503
_00grp
bg503
bgm03
bgm03
_00grp
_00grp
_00grp
b_bg201e
bgm15
bgm15
b_bg201e
bed_gosogoso
_00grp
b_bg201e
_00grp
_00grp
_00com
